can life be truly enjoyed in bits and
parts half a celebration bit of a
vacation part of a
party well life should be enjoyed at its
fullest with holistic freedom and
complete
confidence that's what we are here for
presenting ICICI Lombard's Health advant
Edge
policy a holistic health cover for you
and your loved ones
a policy that comes with Benefits that
cater to your health care as well as
preventive care needs at all
stages with all the hard work you do for
your family and yourself you deserve
extra peace of
mind so with our unlimited reset benefit
you can now restore your balance Su
insured unlimited times for any illness
for some insured above rupe 10 lakhs no
worries just continuous coverage now
enjoy Peace of Mind
worldwide with zero co- payment for
worldwide cover benefit for planned as
well as emergency treatment with no Zone
based co-pay this policy waves customers
payment share in their preferred
treatment Zone with our inbuilt claim
protector get coverage for consumable
items that are otherwise not payable by
us under your claim guaranteed payment
what's more get covered for domestic air
ambulance expenses to nearest hospital
for emergency care as
well with a promise of holistic coverage
we bring you a booket of benefits such
as some insured limit up to rupe 3 cror
age-based pricing guaranteed cumulative
bonus bariatric surgery cover modern
treatments covered lifelong renewability
tax benefit preventive Health checkup
apart from these enhanced features the
Health Advantage policy comes with
optional add-on covers
too choose Health Advantage policy and
ensure holistic protection for yourself
and your family